今じゃ！　やれ！
After you told me, an octopus,
that I was a cool guy...
フン！
I'm gonna save you!
もう我慢できねえ！ じかに　この目で確かめてやる！ 皆さん　落ち着いて。
Huh?! He vanished in an instant...
たった今　「十老頭」と 連絡がとれました。
I can't sense him at all.
中継で直接　「十老頭」から お話があります。
Only the smell of cigarettes. He's gone...
競売は間違いなく 開催されますので
This isn't mere invisibility.
皆さん　落ち着いて　ここ１０階の オークション会場へ　お入りください。
Does he also have the ability to change locations instantly,
without making any sound?
大丈夫　ここは１０階だ
That isn't possible!
階段を降りさえしなければ いいんだ
How did he do it?!
大丈夫だ
When I hold my breath, no one can sense my existence.
[TV]　よぉ　みんな元気か？
You were even touching me... But your mind didn't realize it.
[TV]　まずは連絡の不備を詫びよう すまなかった。
Eh? I touched you?
[TV]　だいぶ　ゴタゴタしちまったが もう大丈夫だ。
You know how some people are easily overlooked?
[TV]　「幻影旅団」の頭は始末した。
When you go to a restaurant in a group, there's always one person that the
waitress forgets to bring water.
お！
This is an extreme version.
[TV]　残りの連中をやるのも 時間の問題。
I'm right here, but no one notices me.
[TV]　狩りは玄人に任せるとして お前らは競売を楽しんでくれ。
Oh... I use my other ability to turn invisible
[TV]　今夜は特別に 俺達も生で見させてもらう。
to cover this one so no one can learn about it.
[TV]　張り切って掘り出し物を 競り落としてくれ。
For the record, you and I are
the only ones in the world
皆さん　お聞きの通りです
who know this.
「十老頭」の面々が　中継先で ご覧になっております
Why tell me something so important?
奮って競売にご参加ください。
Well, it's to build trust.
[無線]
Until you've done due diligence,
don't trust anyone! Huh? I said it's okay, so why are
you being so difficult?
イルミか？
Can you even make this decision on your own?!
[無線] うん　俺の依頼人は？
What about your buddy? He'll have a fit
ここにいる。
when he hears you teamed up with
a suspicious-looking monster...
うぅ。 フン！
And why am I insulting myself?
[無線] あっ　今　戦ってたの？
I didn't choose to be this way!
彼は　まだ生きてる？
He talks a lot...
間一髪か　あ　よかった じゃあ　伝えといて。 「『十老頭』は始末した
Whatever. Even a friend of twenty years
could stab you in the back. Time is no measure of trust!
約束の口座に 入金よろしく」ってね。
Say, "Ho"!
どっこいしょっと やれやれ　お互い命拾いをしたの。
You're no fun... We can never be friends. I feel the same way...
やらなくていいの？
Then, are you sure about this?
わしらの依頼人は「十老頭」。
About what? About teaming up with me.
その依頼人が 死んでしまった以上
Won't your buddy object?
お主は もう　ターゲットではないのでな。
Most likely. Because he tends to be cautious
and to question everything.
そう？　意外だな もうないよ　こんなチャンス。
This won't work, then. The deal's dead in the water.
お主　わしらを快楽殺人者と 勘違いしとらんか？
But if I insist on having my way, it'll be fine. Killua won't like it, but he'll give in.
好きでやっとるわけじゃなし
Really... He must have a hard time.
わしゃ　タダ働きも　タダ死にも まっぴらじゃわい。
Well, whatever.
If you say it's okay, I'll trust you.
俺が　イルミに「十老頭」の暗殺を 依頼したの　知ってたの？
So let's get to business. Yeah.
もちろんじゃ　じゃが それはそれ　これはこれ。
I want to defeat the King.
わしらは　受けた依頼を 遂行するだけじゃ。
Want to know why? Yeah, of course.
なるほどね。
That's what I've been waiting for...
ねぇ　１つ聞いていいかい？ ん？
Revenge.
サシでやったら　俺とあんた どっちが勝つ？ フン　そりゃ十中八九　わしじゃろ。
Right now, I can't tell you
why I want revenge... Okay. I'd like to know, but I'll wait.
お前が本気で わしをやろうと思えば
That's probably what he wants to hear...
話は別じゃがな まったく　ナメたガキじゃ。
If you're that curious, I'll tell you. You'll tell me now?!
やっぱ　バレてた
Just kidding! Beg all you want, but I won't tell you now.
ふぅ…。
His name was Peggy.
しんど！
I saw the King behead him right before my eyes.
ありゃ　盗めねえわ。
But at the time, I didn't realize
what had happened.
[TEL]　じゃあ　エル病院で 待ってればいいのね？
You saw it happen, didn't you?
この後　救急車で　そちらへ運ぶ。
Because I'd forgotten that Peggy
気を失ってるだけで 心配はないが ここで寝かせておくより 病院のほうが　はるかに安全だ。
was the one who raised me.
私も見たかったな
No, I should rephrase that... I've only remembered a few things.
２人が団長と どんな戦いをしたのか。
The names of my parents, my name,
episodes from my childhood.
コルトピ 例のもの用意できるか？
Peggy was the name of the
Chimera Ant the King killed.
もちろん 生命体は無理だけど 動かないものとしてなら。
That was also my foster father's human name.
十分だ あとは手はず通りに。 それと…
He was into education, and always
carried thick books around.
あの娘の乗る救急車は襲うな。
In both life and death, he never
parted with his books about NGL.
行く途中は 本当に安全なんだろうな？
Then you all have memories
from when you were human?
もし救急車を襲う気なら 来る時に仕掛けているはずです。
I don't know if we're all the same.
今なら 流れ弾の心配もないでしょう。
Some Chimera Ants are clearly feral in nature. With others, there's no
telling what they're thinking.
お待たせしました　皆様。
But I think I understand now.
では　これより オークションを開始いたします！
This is why, when we first met,
I was willing to trust you.
早速　本日最初の品を ご紹介いたしましょう。
You're very human. More human than any other
Chimera Ant I've met.
ふぅ… まったく　ヒヤヒヤしたが
In fact, I'd say you're still human.
まぁ　終わり良ければ何とやらだ
Really? When I met you,
I had the opposite reaction.
大幹部連中には １人もケガ人は出なかったんだ
Huh? I could sense a vicious beast inside you.
上出来だろ おっ。
That's why I wanted to team up.
悪いな。
There's no limit to what you'll do.
それでは 次の品をご紹介しましょう！
I'm Gon... Gon Freecss.
ユル国宝館から持ち出された 「純金の処刑刀」！
I actually have one more ability. And the condition for its
activation has been met.
それでは ２０００万からスタート！ ４０００万！ ５０００万！ はい！ ５０００万いただきました！
Time to show you my third power!
あとは自動操作で…　っと　フッ。
Activate!
さぁ　出てまいりました 「青雲文壺」。
It isn't flying away...
２億！ ３億３０００！ ３億８０００！
Does that mean I was using Perfect Plan, too?
おい　お前
This is my third power, God's Accomplice.
競売には参加しねえのか？ どういうことだ？ 「旅団」の頭を始末したんだ そりゃ当然だろ。
While Perfect Plan is active, it allows
anyone I touch to use it, as well.
そんな…　まさか…。
Do you understand how powerful
this technique is now?
今は残党狩りだとよ。 やっぱ　プロは違うねぇ。
This power will let us approach
and attack the enemy...
フフフ…。
without their knowledge.
役立たずの　おめぇらが 救急車だ何だと騒いでる間に ゾルディックの連中が 片付けてくれたぜ。
The King's strength doesn't matter... If we can sneak up and use a powerful
attack when his guard is lowered, we'll win.
…ってなわけで てめぇも　もう用なしだ。
Hey, Gon...
占い女のケツに ひっついとけよ　ボケが。
You're the partner I've been looking for.
とっとと　病院でもホテルでも 行っちまえ　あぁ？ それとも　点数稼ぎに失敗して がっかり来てる
The perfect guy to smack the King with the strongest attack this world's ever seen!
信じない この目で確かめるまで
when you used that rock-paper-scissors thing. Those were my soldiers.
こいつが頭か？ まだ若造じゃねえか
They were killing for sport when
I wasn't paying attention.
ナメたまねしやがって。
They're no longer my soldiers, or even my allies.
おい！ 首から上は傷めつけるなよ ネットで顔　さらすからな。 残党の死体が見つかった！
Well, from their perspective,
I'm the one who's changed.
あ…。 おう　今　行く。
What you said about being your partner...
全部で５体か… こいつらの身元を探れ。
There's someone who'd be better than me.
ＤＮＡ　歯型　指紋　病気 ありとあらゆるとこに照会しろ！
You know someone? Yep.
首から下は　バラしても構わねえ！
I'll contact him. Hold on.
身元が割り出せたら 親　きょうだい
I trust you.
親戚　恋人まで全部殺せ！ 二度とナメた野郎が 現れねえよう
And even if you end up turning on me,
I won't blame you or regret my decision.
念入りに責めて殺すんだ！
Because I watched you, spoke to you,
and decided to trust you.
ハァ　ハァ…。
But I'm not about to trust others
just because you trust them.
ラストの品と なってしまいました！
I get your point, but...
これが　世界７大美色の１つ 「緋の眼」でございます！
My life is on the line here. Listen to me.
クルタ族が滅亡した今 現存するのは　わずか３６対。
Perfect Plan is not invincible. In fact, it's highly vulnerable.
その中でも 強い緋の発色を残す絶品です！
I can make people ignore my existence, but I'm still right there in the same place.
They just don't notice me.
それでは １億ジェニーからスタート！ １億１０００！ [TEL] １億２０００！ [TEL]
So their attacks can still hit me.
１億３０００！ [TEL] １億５０００！ [TEL] ボスですか？　クラピカです。
Knowing there's a person around with
my ability, what would someone do?
申し訳ありません 私の読み違いで
They'd launch attacks in every direction. Oh, you're right...
「クモ」の頭がやられ 競売が予定通り行われています。 [TEL]　何!?
If one of those attacks hits me,
even by dumb luck, I'm done for.
たった今　「緋の眼」が 競りにかけられています。 参加しますか？ [TEL]　無論だ
I hate to admit it, but when it comes to combat,
I'm the weakest Chimera Ant around.
何としても落札しろ！
I'm on the same level as foot soldiers.
予算の上限は？
Forget the King...
[TEL]　ない　いくらでも構わん 競り落とせ！
I couldn't even survive a punch
from a Squadron Leader.
分かりました。 ３億！ さぁ　３億が出ました！
If I just turn invisible,
others can locate me with En.
あとは　いいですか？ ありませんか？
It's been tested, so the other
Squadron Leaders know this, too.
３億５０００！ お！
I need my enemies to believe
my power to be weak.
３億６０００！
They need to think En is enough to beat it.
３億７０００！ ３億９０００！ ５億！ １０億。 うっ!?
This ability is only invincible
if no one knows about it.
フフフ…。 に…　２９億!?
Enough explaining... My point is that I don't want to
reveal my power to any others!
[TEL]　ええ　殺し屋が招集された 部屋にいた　スキンヘッドの男が
Not even if it's someone you trust.
最後まで競って来まして…。
You can see for yourself, then.
ゼンジか　クソ！ 予想外の出費だ…　チクショ あの豚野郎が
I'll call him out here without mentioning you. W-Wait...
まぁ　いいさ
You can watch from a distance.
値段が上がるほど コミュニティーに入る金も多くなり
Hello— Yo! I've been waiting, fool!
それだけ俺の評価も上がる
You pulled a fast one! Where are you?
ネオンの占いさえあれば すぐに取り戻せる金だ
I've got lots of questions for you.
いや　問題ない よくやった　ご苦労。 そうとも　これは先行投資 上へ行くための
Because of you kids, the boss
had to make a move... The plan's been derailed,
but I support what you're doing.
そのためにも　ネオンの機嫌だけは 損ねないようにしなくてはな
Letting five million die isn't right. The boss used his power to surround the capital.
俺の切り札
Really?
これからも　ずっと
That should make it harder for Neferpitou
to control puppets remotely.
これさえあれば…　フフっ
In other words, they can't perform
the selection from a distance. Right.
金など　掃いて捨てるほど 入って来る
But the boss and Knov-san will be expending
all their energy to delay Neferpitou.
ノストラードファミリー様ですね 落札おめでとうございます！
Which means, when the operation starts, they won't be in any condition to
take on any of the Royal Guard.
品物は　こちらでよろしいですね？ ああ。
We expect more citizens to gather
in the capital for the celebration.
てめぇ　このままで帰れると 思ってんのか？
What? You split up? I get it... He's been disrupting things alone. Can you call him real quick?
チッ　止まれ！ 頭　吹っ飛ばすぞ！
No luck. He isn't picking up...
どけ。 ふざけ…　ん？
I think his is off. Really? Well, keep trying.
うっ！
We should meet up, the sooner the better.
やめておけ 誰でもいい気分なんだ。 いぃ…！
Yeah. Let's find a halfway point to meet.
別に　お前でも。
Here... Mandai City.
うぅ…　あ…。
Okay, got it.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Checkmate.
あいつは　一体…。
You're done.
ハッハッハ…！
Why didn't you resign?
こいつら…
Don't make me repeat myself.
ひとが捕まってた時に 酒盛りしてたんか。 おう！　戻ったか。
The match ended twenty-two moves ago.
いやいや　ほら お前らも　飲め飲め！
Why did you not resign then?
アホか　俺達　未成年だっての！
Did you believe I would make a mistake?
おめぇら よく無事で帰って来れたな。
Idiot.
そんなにヤバい連中なのか 「幻影旅団」って。
Next, we have the national Go champion.
ゼパイルさんに教わった 殺し技なんだ。 あ？
Give me the rulebook. It may look simple at first,
but it is a complex game.
) )
It may take more time to learn than shogi.
経験は　時に盲点を生む。
Please let me leave! What do you want?
「旅団」攻略に　贋作のノウハウが 参考になるかもな。 そう！　贋作は　奥が深い！
Someone! Help me!
俺だって　ただ　だらだら 飲んでたわけじゃないぜ。
My glasses... Silence.
ゼパイルから いろいろと教わったのさ！
You are in the King's presence.
うん…。 行きたいんだけど　クラピカに会って 「念」を教わらなきゃ。
The choice is yours.
クラピカ？　連絡とれたのか。
Sit across from me now.
うん　あっちからの 電話待ちなんだけどね。
Or die.
あいつだって 「念」を覚えたの最近だろ？
5.5 points. The King wins.
それでも　クラピカは 「旅団」の１人を倒してるんだよ。
I-It only took him ten games?
マジか!?
I'm t-tired!
ああ…　何か秘密があるはずなんだ 「念」にはさ。
It's the only explanation for that loss! And I think I have a fever. I'm short on sleep.
経験やパワー以外の 「念」独特の強さがね。
And I feel dizzy... I'll give you eight hours. And any medicine you need.
アッハ！　やった！
Should you lose again, I won't
be interested in excuses.
パパ　ありがとう！ ウフっ　キレイ。
Rest as if your life depends on it.
うん　許してあげる。 そうか これでパパも　ひと安心だ。
I'm impressed by how quickly
you learn these games.
ウフフフ　フフフ…。
I can't believe it took less than half
the time you spent mastering shogi.
ご苦労だった 娘の体も大丈夫そうだから
It's all about learning the feel. Chess, Go, shogi...
これから ホテルに戻ることにする。 あとは　明日。
They have different rules, but all three
「俳優の使用済みティッシュ」を 競り落として　競売は終了だ。
have a certain rhythm to their moves.
俺は　明後日の午前中に ここをたつが
That means disrupting your
opponent's rhythm is crucial.
お前達は　しばらく 娘の買い物に付き合ってくれ。
Once you've learned the openings,
you can deduce your opponent's rhythm.
うっ…。 えっ！
Once you know their rhythm,
you need only disrupt it.
クラピカ　残りの競売と 買い物の付き添いは
If you've already reached that conclusion,
I don't see the benefit of playing more games.
私達でやるから しばらく１人で休んだら？
I believe they will only bore you.
そうか…
How many remain?
すまないが　そうさせてもらう。
This country has one more professional game. It's a board game called Gungi.
大丈夫か？　あいつ。
Gungi?
[TEL]
The game originated in East Gorteau, and nearly all citizens know how to play. Give me the rulebook.
[TEL]　もしもし　クラピカ？
As in chess and shogi, its goal is to trap the king.
ああ。
But you can stack up to three pieces.
「旅団」を止めたいと言ってたな。
At the start, you may also freely place
your pieces within your own area.
だが　その必要はなくなったよ。
The game has a different feel
「クモ」は死んだ。 [TEL]　えっ？　どういうこと？ クラピカ！
due to the addition of a third dimension.
[TEL] うん　残念。
For the past fifteen years,
there have been world tournaments, and East Gorteau has yet to lose.
慰めてあげようと思ったのに。
Currently, they're on their third representative,
a five-time reigning champion.
マフィアンコミュニティー 大したことなかったね。
Then, if I defeat this champion,
I'll be the best in the world?
ノブナガが　いなくても 十分だったよ。
A fitting way to end this recreation.
うるせぇ！
Bring them in.
クラピカは　今　言いようのない むなしさを抱えていた
There are six days until the selection. The King has no idea